<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2012 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="comm">
  <message>
    <entry key="noninteger">TracebackStagesPerPipeline must be a positive integer</entry>
    <entry key="toolarge">No pipeline register will be added since the value
                          of TracebackStagesPerPipeline is greater than traceback
                          depth</entry>
    <entry key="defaultvalue">Default value of TracebackStagesPerPipeline is set to 4</entry>
    <entry key="nonrecursivetrellis">HDL support requires a non recursive trellis</entry>
    <entry key="coderate">HDL support requires a decoding rate from 1/2 to 1/7</entry>
    <entry key="constraintlength">HDL support requires a constraint length between 3 and 9</entry>
    <entry key="DSinputnotsupport">HDL support is not available for Double/Single input data types</entry>
    <entry key="signedinputnotsupport">HDL support is not available for Signed input data types</entry>
    <entry key="onlysupportUfixN">HDL support requires the input port word length to be equal
                  to the number of soft decision bits.</entry>
    <entry key="Dectypenotsupport">HDL support is not available for the Unquantized Decision type</entry>
    <entry key="replacestmetWL">The state metric word length has been set to {0}
                  bits in the HDL code</entry>
    <entry key="stmetWLtoosmall">HDL support requires the state metric word length to
                                 be at least {0} bits</entry>
    <entry key="resettypeunsupported">HDL support requires the reset signal to be boolean</entry>
    <entry key="resetmodeunsupported">HDL support requires that the reset action be
                                      delayed to the next time step. This will lead to
                                      a synchronous reset in the HDL code.</entry>
    <entry key="erasureunsupported">HDL support is not available for the erasures input port</entry>
    <entry key="latencyinfo">The generated HDL output has a delay of {0} samples with
                  respect to the original Viterbi Decoder output.</entry>
    <entry key="tbdtoosmall">HDL support requires the traceback depth to be greater than
        or equal to the constraint length</entry>
    <entry key="truncatedmode">HDL support is not available for the Truncated operation mode</entry>
    <entry key="terminatedmode">HDL support is not available for the Terminated operation mode</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
